<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>{static is} The New Dynamic</title>
    <description>Following the Post-CMS paradigm</description>
    <link>http://budparr.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://budparr.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Scheduled</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This post is scheduled to be published in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It should not be displayed by the theme.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://budparr.com/tests-content/1400-scheduled/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://budparr.com/tests-content/1400-scheduled/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello Again</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the end of the thing. Nor did such soothing scenes, however temporary, fail of at least as temporary an effect on Ahab. But if these secret golden keys did seem to open in him his own secret golden treasuries, yet did his breath upon them prove but tarnishing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, grassy glades! oh, ever vernal endless landscapes in the soul; in ye,—though long parched by the dead drought of the earthy life,—in ye, men yet may roll, like young horses in new morning clover; and for some few fleeting moments, feel the cool dew of the life immortal on them. Would to God these blessed calms would last. But the mingled, mingling threads of life are woven by warp and woof: calms crossed by storms, a storm for every calm. There is no steady unretracing progress in this life; we do not advance through fixed gradations, and at the last one pause:—through infancy’s unconscious spell, boyhood’s thoughtless faith, adolescence’ doubt (the common doom), then scepticism, then disbelief, resting at last in manhood’s pondering repose of If. But once gone through, we trace the round again; and are infants, boys, and men, and Ifs eternally. Where lies the final harbor, whence we unmoor no more? In what rapt ether sails the world, of which the weariest will never weary? Where is the foundling’s father hidden? Our souls are like those orphans whose unwedded mothers die in bearing them: the secret of our paternity lies in their grave, and we must there to learn it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that same day, too, gazing far down from his boat’s side into that same golden sea, Starbuck lowly murmured:—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Loveliness unfathomable, as ever lover saw in his young bride’s eye!—Tell me not of thy teeth-tiered sharks, and thy kidnapping cannibal ways. Let faith oust fact; let fancy oust memory; I look deep down and do believe.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And Stubb, fish-like, with sparkling scales, leaped up in that same golden light:—&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I am Stubb, and Stubb has his history; but here Stubb takes oaths that he has always been jolly!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And jolly enough were the sights and the sounds that came bearing down before the wind, some few weeks after Ahab’s harpoon had been welded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a Nantucket ship, the Bachelor, which had just wedged in her last cask of oil, and bolted down her bursting hatches; and now, in glad holiday apparel, was joyously, though somewhat vain-gloriously, sailing round among the widely-separated ships on the ground, previous to pointing her prow for home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The three men at her mast-head wore long streamers of narrow red bunting at their hats; from the stern, a whale-boat was suspended, bottom down; and hanging captive from the bowsprit was seen the long lower jaw of the last whale they had slain. Signals, ensigns, and jacks of all colours were flying from her rigging, on every side. Sideways lashed in each of her three basketed tops were two barrels of sperm; above which, in her top-mast cross-trees, you saw slender breakers of the same precious fluid; and nailed to her main truck was a brazen lamp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As was afterwards learned, the Bachelor had met with the most surprising success; all the more wonderful, for that while cruising in the same seas numerous other vessels had gone entire months without securing a single fish. Not only had barrels of beef and bread been given away to make room for the far more valuable sperm, but additional supplemental casks had been bartered for, from the ships she had met; and these were stowed along the deck, and in the captain’s and officers’ state-rooms. Even the cabin table itself had been knocked into kindling-wood; and the cabin mess dined off the broad head of an oil-butt, lashed down to the floor for a centrepiece. In the forecastle, the sailors had actually caulked and pitched their chests, and filled them; it was humorously added, that the cook had clapped a head on his largest boiler, and filled it; that the steward had plugged his spare coffee-pot and filled it; that the harpooneers had headed the sockets of their irons and filled them; that indeed everything was filled with sperm, except the captain’s pantaloons pockets, and those he reserved to thrust his hands into, in self-complacent testimony of his entire satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://budparr.com/tests-content/hello-again/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://budparr.com/tests-content/hello-again/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Another Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As co-chairs of the House Sovereignty Caucus, we are concerned about the impact the U.N. Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities (Disabilities Treaty) will have on U.S. sovereignty and freedom. Reports have been circulating that the U.S. Senate plans to consider the Disabilities Treaty in early November even though it was defeated in the 112th Congress. We believe that joining the treaty will not enhance the rights of Americans with disabilities nor advance U.S. national interests abroad. Instead, the treaty’s vague definitions of “disability” and “sexual and reproductive health” invite abuse and the furtherance of abortion as a right, and Article 7 threatens Americans’ parental rights. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Disabilities Treaty establishes a body of unaccountable experts, the Committee on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities, which evaluates the compliance of state parties to the treaty every four years, and issues recommendations for how they might improve in fulfilling their obligations. We are concerned that joining the treaty will allow foreign experts to interfere with U.S. policymaking and violate the principles of U.S. sovereignty. Too often U.N. treaty bodies seek to broaden the scope of the treaties that created them through treaty monitoring bodies, which expand language in original agreements and disregard national sovereignty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, we find the language in the treaty especially concerning because it lacks concise definitions of very important terms. For example, the Disabilities Treaty lacks a clear definition of “disability,” which it defines as an evolving concept. This ambiguity invites abuse by persons or groups that do not suffer from a recognized medical disability but seek resources and protection under the authority of the treaty. This could also result in complicating the implementation of the treaty in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although the treaty’s main purpose seeks to ensure the rights and protections of the disabled, the Disabilities Treaty includes the issue of sexual and reproductive health, which some U.N. staff has interpreted as “abortion rights.” While the nations who negotiated the treaty expressly rejected that interpretation, there is reason to believe the treaty monitoring body will read a right to abortion into the treaty like other treaty monitoring bodies have done for treaties that do not even include the controversial phrase. Abortion advocates and U.N. staff have already pointed to the Disabilities Treaty as a means to further build their case in favor of abortion as a human right. We strongly oppose this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are also concerned that Article 7 of the treaty would give the federal government the ability to override the decisions of parents of disabled children if the government believes its views are in the best interest of the child. This could strip parents of fundamental rights, including the ability to home school their children with disabilities if they believe it is in the best interests of their child. We support the rights of the disabled within the U.S., and the U.S. already holds itself to a high standard of human rights. We believe that the rights of Americans with disabilities are well protected under existing law and are enforced by a range of state and federal agencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any modification or expansion of protections to Americans with disabilities should be achieved through the legislative process – not through an international treaty. Allowing an international panel of disability experts to scrutinize the U.S. record every four years could result in many unintended consequences for U.S. interests, yielding little or no benefit in realizing disability rights for Americans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all, we believe that U.S. ratification of the Disabilities Treaty would not advance U.S. national interests abroad or the rights of Americans with disabilities here at home. This treaty would subject the U.S. to further intrusion by U.N. officials into policies that are sensitive domestic and social issues, and we remain convinced that the risks to the U.S. posed by this treaty far outweigh any potential benefits that could be realized by U.S. ratification.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://budparr.com/tests-content/another-post/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://budparr.com/tests-content/another-post/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Proin at eros non eros adipiscing mollis. Donec semper turpis sed diam. Sed consequat ligula nec tortor. Integer eget sem. Ut vitae enim eu est vehicula gravida. Morbi ipsum ipsum, porta nec, tempor id, auctor vitae, purus. Pellentesque neque. Nulla luctus erat vitae libero. Integer nec enim. Phasellus aliquam enim et tortor. Quisque aliquet, quam elementum condimentum feugiat, tellus odio consectetuer wisi, vel nonummy sem neque in elit. Curabitur eleifend wisi iaculis ipsum. Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. In non velit non ligula laoreet ultrices. Praesent ultricies facilisis nisl. Vivamus luctus elit sit amet mi. Phasellus pellentesque, erat eget elementum volutpat, dolor nisl porta neque, vitae sodales ipsum nibh in ligula. Maecenas mattis pulvinar diam. Curabitur sed leo.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://budparr.com/tests-content/hello-world/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://budparr.com/tests-content/hello-world/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Page Image Alignment</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to image alignment! The best way to demonstrate the ebb and flow of the various image positioning options is to nestle them snuggly among an ocean of words. Grab a paddle and let’s get started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the topic of alignment, it should be noted that users can choose from the options ofÂ &lt;em&gt;None&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Left&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Right, &lt;/em&gt;andÂ &lt;em&gt;Center&lt;/em&gt;. In addition, they also get the options ofÂ &lt;em&gt;Thumbnail&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Medium&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Large&lt;/em&gt;Â &amp;amp;Â &lt;em&gt;Fullsize&lt;/em&gt;.
&amp;lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&amp;gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-906 aligncenter&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-580x300.jpg&quot; width=&quot;580&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
The image above happens to beÂ &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;centered&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-904 alignleft&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-150x150.jpg&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The rest of this paragraph is fillerÂ for the sake of seeing the text wrap around the 150x150 image, which is &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;left aligned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.Â &lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“As you can see the should be some space above”, below, and to the right of the image. The text should not be creeping on the image. Creeping is just not right. Images need breathing room too. Let them speak like you words. Let them do their jobs without any hassle from the text. In about one moreÂ sentenceÂ here, we’ll see that the text moves from the right of the image down below the image inÂ seamlessÂ transition. Again, letting the do it’s thang.Â Mission accomplished!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now for a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;massively large image&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. It also has &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;no alignment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;alignnone  wp-image-907&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-1200x4002.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1200&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image above, though 1200px wide, should not overflow the content area. It should remain contained with no visible disruption to the flow of content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-905 alignright&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-300x200.jpg&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now we’re going to shift things to the &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;right align&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Again, there should be plenty of room above, below, and to the left of the image. Just look at him there… Hey guy! Way to rock that right side. I don’t care what the left aligned image says, you look great. Don’t let anyone else tell you differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In just a bit here, you should see the text start to wrap below the right aligned image and settle in nicely. There should still be plenty of room and everything should be sitting pretty.Â Yeah… Just like that. It never felt so good to be right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And just when you thought we were done, we’re going to do them all over again with captions!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=”attachment_906” align=”aligncenter” width=”580”]&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-906  &quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-580x300.jpg&quot; width=&quot;580&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt; Look at 580x300 getting some &lt;a title=&quot;Image Settings&quot; href=&quot;http://en.support.wordpress.com/images/image-settings/&quot;&gt;caption&lt;/a&gt; love.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image above happens to beÂ &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;centered&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. The caption also has a link in it, just to see if it does anything funky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=”attachment_904” align=”alignleft” width=”150”]&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-904  &quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-150x150.jpg&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; /&gt; Itty-bitty caption.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The rest of this paragraph is fillerÂ for the sake of seeing the text wrap around the 150x150 image, which is &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;left aligned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.Â &lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see the should be some space above, below, and to the right of the image. The text should not be creeping on the image. Creeping is just not right. Images need breathing room too. Let them speak like you words. Let them do their jobs without any hassle from the text. In about one moreÂ sentenceÂ here, we’ll see that the text moves from the right of the image down below the image inÂ seamlessÂ transition. Again, letting the do it’s thang. Mission accomplished!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now for a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;massively large image&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. It also has &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;no alignment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=”attachment_907” align=”alignnone” width=”1200”]&lt;img class=&quot; wp-image-907&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-1200x4002.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1200&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt; Massive image comment for your eyeballs.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image above, though 1200px wide, should not overflow the content area. It should remain contained with no visible disruption to the flow of content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=”attachment_905” align=”alignright” width=”300”]&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-905 &quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-300x200.jpg&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt; Feels good to be right all the time.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now we’re going to shift things to the &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;right align&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Again, there should be plenty of room above, below, and to the left of the image. Just look at him there… Hey guy! Way to rock that right side. I don’t care what the left aligned image says, you look great. Don’t let anyone else tell you differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In just a bit here, you should see the text start to wrap below the right aligned image and settle in nicely. There should still be plenty of room and everything should be sitting pretty. Yeah… Just like that. It never felt so good to be right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that’s a wrap, yo! You survived theÂ tumultuousÂ waters of alignment. Image alignment achievement unlocked!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://budparr.com/tests-content/1919-page-image-alignment/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://budparr.com/tests-content/1919-page-image-alignment/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Markup: HTML Tags and Formatting</title>
        <description>&lt;h2&gt;Headings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Header one&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Header two&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Header three&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Header four&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Header five&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;Header six&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Single line blockquote:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;Stay hungry. Stay foolish.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Multi line blockquote with a cite reference:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;People think focus means saying yes to the thing you&#39;ve got to focus on. But that&#39;s not what it means at all. It means saying no to the hundred other good ideas that there are. You have to pick carefully. I&#39;m actually as proud of the things we haven&#39;t done as the things I have done. Innovation is saying no to 1,000 things. &lt;cite&gt;Steve Jobs - Apple Worldwide Developers&#39; Conference, 1997&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tables&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
	&lt;thead&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;th&gt;Employee&lt;/th&gt;
			&lt;th&gt;Salary&lt;/th&gt;
			&lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/thead&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://example.org/&quot;&gt;John Doe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;$1&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;Because that&#39;s all Steve Jobs needed for a salary.&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://example.org/&quot;&gt;Jane Doe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;$100K&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;For all the blogging she does.&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://example.org/&quot;&gt;Fred Bloggs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;$100M&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;Pictures are worth a thousand words, right? So Jane x 1,000.&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://example.org/&quot;&gt;Jane Bloggs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;$100B&lt;/td&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;With hair like that?! Enough said...&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Definition Lists&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;&lt;dt&gt;Definition List Title&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;Definition list division.&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;Startup&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;A startup company or startup is a company or temporary organization designed to search for a repeatable and scalable business model.&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;#dowork&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;Coined by Rob Dyrdek and his personal body guard Christopher &quot;Big Black&quot; Boykins, &quot;Do Work&quot; works as a self motivator, to motivating your friends.&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;dt&gt;Do It Live&lt;/dt&gt;&lt;dd&gt;I&#39;ll let Bill O&#39;Reilly will &lt;a title=&quot;We&#39;ll Do It Live&quot; href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O_HyZ5aW76c&quot;&gt;explain&lt;/a&gt; this one.&lt;/dd&gt;&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Unordered Lists (Nested)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item one
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item one
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item one&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Ordered List (Nested)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item one
&lt;ol&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item one
&lt;ol&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item one&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item two&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item three&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;List item four&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;HTML Tags&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These supported tags come from the WordPress.com code &lt;a title=&quot;Code&quot; href=&quot;http://en.support.wordpress.com/code/&quot;&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Address Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;address&gt;1 Infinite Loop
Cupertino, CA 95014
United States&lt;/address&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anchor Tag (aka. Link)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an example of a &lt;a title=&quot;Apple&quot; href=&quot;http://apple.com&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abbreviation Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The abbreviation &lt;abbr title=&quot;Seriously&quot;&gt;srsly&lt;/abbr&gt; stands for “seriously”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acronym Tag (&lt;em&gt;deprecated in HTML5&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The acronym &lt;acronym title=&quot;For The Win&quot;&gt;ftw&lt;/acronym&gt; stands for “for the win”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Big TagÂ &lt;strong&gt;(&lt;em&gt;deprecated in HTML5&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These tests are a &lt;big&gt;big&lt;/big&gt; deal, but this tag is no longer supported in HTML5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cite Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Code is poetry.” –&lt;cite&gt;Automattic&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Code Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will learn later on in these tests that &lt;code&gt;word-wrap: break-word;&lt;/code&gt; will be your best friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Delete Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tag will let you &lt;del&gt;strikeout text&lt;/del&gt;, but this tag is no longer supported in HTML5 (use the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;strike&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; instead).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Emphasize Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The emphasize tag should &lt;em&gt;italicize&lt;/em&gt; text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insert Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tag should denote &lt;ins&gt;inserted&lt;/ins&gt; text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keyboard Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This scarsly known tag emulates &lt;kbd&gt;keyboard text&lt;/kbd&gt;, which is usually styled like the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;code&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preformatted Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tag styles large blocks of code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;.post-title {
	margin: 0 0 5px;
	font-weight: bold;
	font-size: 38px;
	line-height: 1.2;
	and here&#39;s a line of some really, really, really, really long text, just to see how the PRE tag handles it and to find out how it overflows;
}&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quote Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;q&gt;Developers, developers, developers…&lt;/q&gt; –Steve Ballmer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strike TagÂ &lt;strong&gt;(&lt;em&gt;deprecated in HTML5&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tag shows &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration:line-through;&quot;&gt;strike-through text&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strong Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This tag shows &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;strong&gt; text.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscript Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting our science styling on with H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O, which should push the “2” down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Superscript Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still sticking with science and Isaac Newton’s E = MC&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;, which should lift the 2 up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Teletype TagÂ &lt;strong&gt;(&lt;em&gt;deprecated in HTML5&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This rarely used tag emulates &lt;tt&gt;teletype text&lt;/tt&gt;, which is usually styled like the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;code&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Variable Tag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This allows you to denote &lt;var&gt;variables&lt;/var&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://budparr.com/tests-content/2222-markup-html-tags-and-formatting/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://budparr.com/tests-content/2222-markup-html-tags-and-formatting/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Markup: Image Alignment</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;Welcome to image alignment! The best way to demonstrate the ebb and flow of the various image positioning options is to nestle them snuggly among an ocean of words. Grab a paddle and let’s get started.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the topic of alignment, it should be noted that users can choose from the options ofÂ &lt;em&gt;None&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Left&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Right, &lt;/em&gt;andÂ &lt;em&gt;Center&lt;/em&gt;. In addition, they also get the options ofÂ &lt;em&gt;Thumbnail&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Medium&lt;/em&gt;,Â &lt;em&gt;Large&lt;/em&gt;Â &amp;amp;Â &lt;em&gt;Fullsize&lt;/em&gt;.
&amp;lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&amp;gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-906 aligncenter&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-580x300.jpg&quot; width=&quot;580&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
The image above happens to beÂ &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;centered&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-904 alignleft&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-150x150.jpg&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The rest of this paragraph is fillerÂ for the sake of seeing the text wrap around the 150x150 image, which is &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;left aligned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.Â &lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see the should be some space above, below, and to the right of the image. The text should not be creeping on the image. Creeping is just not right. Images need breathing room too. Let them speak like you words. Let them do their jobs without any hassle from the text. In about one moreÂ sentenceÂ here, we’ll see that the text moves from the right of the image down below the image inÂ seamlessÂ transition. Again, letting the do it’s thang.Â Mission accomplished!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now for a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;massively large image&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. It also has &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;no alignment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;alignnone  wp-image-907&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-1200x4002.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1200&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image above, though 1200px wide, should not overflow the content area. It should remain contained with no visible disruption to the flow of content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-905 alignright&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-300x200.jpg&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now we’re going to shift things to the &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;right align&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Again, there should be plenty of room above, below, and to the left of the image. Just look at him there… Hey guy! Way to rock that right side. I don’t care what the left aligned image says, you look great. Don’t let anyone else tell you differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In just a bit here, you should see the text start to wrap below the right aligned image and settle in nicely. There should still be plenty of room and everything should be sitting pretty.Â Yeah… Just like that. It never felt so good to be right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And just when you thought we were done, we’re going to do them all over again with captions!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=”attachment_906” align=”aligncenter” width=”580”]&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-906  &quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 580x300&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-580x300.jpg&quot; width=&quot;580&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt; Look at 580x300 getting some &lt;a title=&quot;Image Settings&quot; href=&quot;http://en.support.wordpress.com/images/image-settings/&quot;&gt;caption&lt;/a&gt; love.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image above happens to beÂ &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;centered&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. The caption also has a link in it, just to see if it does anything funky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=”attachment_904” align=”alignleft” width=”150”]&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-904  &quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 150x150&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-150x150.jpg&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; /&gt; Itty-bitty caption.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The rest of this paragraph is fillerÂ for the sake of seeing the text wrap around the 150x150 image, which is &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;left aligned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.Â &lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see the should be some space above, below, and to the right of the image. The text should not be creeping on the image. Creeping is just not right. Images need breathing room too. Let them speak like you words. Let them do their jobs without any hassle from the text. In about one moreÂ sentenceÂ here, we’ll see that the text moves from the right of the image down below the image inÂ seamlessÂ transition. Again, letting the do it’s thang. Mission accomplished!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now for a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;massively large image&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. It also has &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;no alignment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=”attachment_907” align=”alignnone” width=”1200”]&lt;img class=&quot; wp-image-907&quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 1200x400&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-1200x4002.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1200&quot; height=&quot;400&quot; /&gt; Massive image comment for your eyeballs.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image above, though 1200px wide, should not overflow the content area. It should remain contained with no visible disruption to the flow of content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[caption id=”attachment_905” align=”alignright” width=”300”]&lt;img class=&quot;size-full wp-image-905 &quot; title=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; alt=&quot;Image Alignment 300x200&quot; src=&quot;http://wpthemetestdata.files.wordpress.com/2013/03/image-alignment-300x200.jpg&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; /&gt; Feels good to be right all the time.[/caption]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now we’re going to shift things to the &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;right align&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Again, there should be plenty of room above, below, and to the left of the image. Just look at him there… Hey guy! Way to rock that right side. I don’t care what the left aligned image says, you look great. Don’t let anyone else tell you differently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In just a bit here, you should see the text start to wrap below the right aligned image and settle in nicely. There should still be plenty of room and everything should be sitting pretty. Yeah… Just like that. It never felt so good to be right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that’s a wrap, yo! You survived theÂ tumultuousÂ waters of alignment. Image alignment achievement unlocked!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://budparr.com/tests-content/2215-markup-image-alignment/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://budparr.com/tests-content/2215-markup-image-alignment/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Markup: Text Alignment</title>
        <description>&lt;h3&gt;Default&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a paragraph. It should not have any alignment of any kind. It should just flow like you would normally expect. Nothing fancy. Just straight up text, free flowing, with love. Completely neutral and not picking a side or sitting on the fence. It just is. It just freaking is. It likes where it is. It does not feel compelled to pick a side. Leave him be. It will just be better that way. Trust me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Left Align&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:left;&quot;&gt;This is a paragraph. It is left aligned. Because of this, it is a bit more liberal in it&#39;s views. It&#39;s favorite color is green. Left align tends to be more eco-friendly, but it provides no concrete evidence that it really is. Even though it likes share the wealth evenly, it leaves the equal distribution up to justified alignment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Center Align&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;This is a paragraph. It is center aligned. Center is, but nature, a fence sitter. A flip flopper. It has a difficult time making up its mind. It wants to pick a side. Really, it does. It has the best intentions, but it tends to complicate matters more than help. The best you can do is try to win it over and hope for the best. I hear center align does take bribes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Right Align&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:right;&quot;&gt;This is a paragraph. It is right aligned. It is a bit more conservative in it&#39;s views. It&#39;s prefers to not be told what to do or how to do it. Right align totally owns a slew of guns and loves to head to the range for some practice. Which is cool and all. I mean, it&#39;s a pretty good shot from at least four or five football fields away. Dead on. So boss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Justify Align&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:justify;&quot;&gt;This is a paragraph. It is justify aligned. It gets really mad when people associate it with Justin Timberlake. Typically, justified is pretty straight laced. It likes everything to be in it&#39;s place and not all cattywampusÂ like the rest of the aligns. I am not saying that makes it better than the rest of the aligns, but it does tend to put off more of anÂ elitistÂ attitude.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://budparr.com/tests-content/1100-markup-text-alignment/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://budparr.com/tests-content/1100-markup-text-alignment/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Markup: Title With Markup</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Verify that:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;The post title renders the word &quot;with&quot; in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;italics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt; and the word &quot;markup&quot; in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;line-height:1.714285714;font-size:1rem;&quot;&gt;The post title markup should be removed from the browser window / tab.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://budparr.com/tests-content/1200-markup-title-with-markup/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://budparr.com/tests-content/1200-markup-title-with-markup/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Template: Featured Image (Vertical)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This post should display aÂ &lt;a title=&quot;Featured Images&quot; href=&quot;http://en.support.wordpress.com/featured-images/#setting-a-featured-image&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;featured image&lt;/a&gt;, if the themeÂ &lt;a title=&quot;Post Thumbnails&quot; href=&quot;http://codex.wordpress.org/Post_Thumbnails&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;supports it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non-square images can provide some unique styling issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post tests a vertical featured image.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://budparr.com/tests-content/1836-template-featured-image-vertical/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://budparr.com/tests-content/1836-template-featured-image-vertical/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
